Review Exercise L. Four-Word Phrase Story. Little Red Riding Hood. Repeat after me.
Once upon a time, there was a cute little redhead named Little Red Riding Hood. One
day she told her mother that she wanted to take a well-stocked picnic basket to her
dear old grandmother on the other side of the dark, scary black forest. Her mother
warned her not to talk to strangers, especially the dangerous big bad wolf.
Little Red Riding Hood said she'd be careful and left. Halfway there, she saw a
mild-mannered hitchhiker. She pulled over in her bright red sports car and offered
him a ride. Just before they got to the freeway turnoff for her old grandmother's
house, the heavily bearded young man jumped out and ran away. Was he the wolf?
He hurried ahead to the waiting grandmother's house, let himself in, ate
her, and jumped into her bed to wait for Little Red Riding Hood. When Little Red
Riding Hood got to the house, She was surprised. Grandmother, what big eyes you
have! The wolf replied, The better to see you with, my dear. But Grandmother, what
big ears you have! The better to hear you with, my dear. Oh, Grandmother, what big
teeth you have! The better to eat you with! And the wolf jumped out of the bed
to eat Little Red Riding Hood. Fortunately for her, she was a recently paid up member
of the infamous National Rifle Association, so she pulled out her brand
new shotgun and shot the wolf dead.